你已经实现了mainActivity的线框图，
You've implemented the main
activity wireframe, so
所以现在我们可以继续来实现DetailActivity的线框图。
now we can move onto
the detail activity wireframe.
这是他看起来的样子。
This is what it looks like.
我们有日期，最高和最低问题，以及
We have the date, the high and
low temperatures, and
额外天气信息。
then additional weather information.
我们也有天气图标和天气预报。
We also have the weather icon,
and the weather forecast.
这些线是水平的。
And these line up horizontally.
为这个线框图创建layout XML
Build up the layout XML for
this wire frame.
然后修改DetailFragments，然后就可以把所有这些信息放上去，
Then modify the detail fragments that
you can populate all this information,
包括这些心的视图。
including these new views.
当你在这么做的时候，你也需要把DetailFragment移到
While you're doing that, you might as
well move the detail fragment into its
他自己的文件里去，所以他就和DetailActivity区分开来。
own file, so
it's separate from the detail activity.
在你开始之前，我想指出这个布局包含的
Before you get started, I want to point
out that this layout has the information
信息要花很多垂直空间。
taking up a lot of vertical space.
如果你把你的设备旋转为水平模式，
If you rotate your device
into landscape mode, or
或者你有一个高度更小的设备，
you have a smaller height device,.
其中有些信息会被裁剪。
Some of the content could get cut off.
所以想想你该如何让这个视图垂直可滚动。
So think about how you can make this
layout be vertically scrollable.
为了想你展示我是什么意思，
To show you what I mean,
我在布局地步多添加了几行文本。
I added a couple of more lines of
text at the bottom of the layout.
然后我让内容垂直可滚动。
Then I made the content
vertically scrollable.
于是你就可以看到所有的信息。
So you could see all the information.
所以继续吧，在你自己的布局里也这么做。
So go ahead and
make that change to your layout as well.
在你完成所有这些步骤之后，这是应用看起来的样子。
When you're done with all these steps,
this is what the App should look like.
我们现在不在乎视觉细节。
We don't care about
the visual details now.
我们只是想确定功能衔接恰当，
We just want to make sure that
the functionality is hooked up, so
这样所有正确信息都在屏幕上显示出来了。
all the right information
is displayed on screen.
你可以使用下面提供的代码片段用于辅助方法
You can use the code snippets provided
below for helper functions and
以及你之后会用到的字符串。
strings that you're going to need.
并且，留下一个占位图现在也是可以的。
And again, leaving a place
holder image is fine for now.